doordash.com 2014-03-26

# DoorDash Food Delivery | Privacy Policy

### Privacy Policy

Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to the http://www.doordash.com and Palo Alto Delivery Inc. and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to DoorDash include http://www.doordash.com and Palo Alto Delivery, Inc. The DoorDash website is a restaurant food delivery site. By using the DoorDash website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement. 

DoorDash may collect personally identifiable information, such as your name. If you purchase DoorDash's products and services, we collect address, billing and credit card information. This information is used to complete the purchase transaction. We may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future. 

Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by DoorDash. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the DoorDash website. 

DoorDash encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to fromDoorDash so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. DoorDash is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the DoorDash website. 

DoorDash collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the services you have requested. 

DoorDash may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from DoorDash and its affiliates. DoorDash may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered. 

DoorDash does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. 

DoorDash may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to DoorDash, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information. 

DoorDash may keep track of the websites and pages our users visit within DoorDash, in order to determine what DoorDash services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within DoorDash to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area. 

DoorDash will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on DoorDash or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of DoorDash; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of DoorDash, or the public. 

The DoorDash website may use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. 

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize DoorDash pages, or register with DoorDash site or services, a cookie helps DoorDash to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same DoorDash website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the DoorDash features that you customized. 

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the DoorDash services or websites you visit. 

Your personal information is extremely important to us. DoorDash secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol. Although we try our best to protect your information, we cannot completely eliminate security risks associated with personal information. 

DoorDash does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website. 

We respect your privacy and give you an opportunity to opt-out of receiving announcements of certain information. Users may opt-out of receiving any or all communications from DoorDash by contacting us at  [ http://www.doordash.com/contact](http://www.doordash.com/contact). 

DoorDash will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. DoorDash encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how DoorDash is protecting your information. 

DoorDash welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that DoorDash has not adhered to this Statement, please contact DoorDash at: 

**Palo Alto Delivery, Inc**  
565 Stanford Ave.  
Palo Alto, California 94306  

Email Address: support@doordash.com

Telephone Number: +1 (650) 681-9470

Effective as of August 04, 2013
